Guide to the Don Gale KSL editorial video collection 1938-2010 1978-1997
Multimedia Archives, J. Willard Marriott Library, University of Utah
- KSL editorials, 1978-1998; 2010
  - KSL editorials, 1980 May-1980 June; DVD (Disc 12)
    - False promise of public power, 1980 June 18 (Video 49)
    - The power of the bureaucracy, 1980 June 19 (Video 50)
    - The governor and the MX, 1980 June 20 (Video 51)
    - How to make a better integrated circuit, 1980 June 21 (Video 52)
    - The real generation gap, 1980 June 22 (Video 53)
    - Delays in the coal boom, 1980 June 23 (Video 54)
    - Soul-searching over "marriage tax", 1980 June 24 (Video 55)
    - "What's to eat?", 1980 June 25 (Video 56)
    - Trash cleanup in the canyons, 1980 June 26 (Video 57)
    - Where else but in America, 1980 June 27 (Video 58)
    - Solutions versus remedies, 1980 June 28 (Video 59)
    - Senator Proxmire's "golden fleece", 1980 June 29 (Video 60)
    - The price of delay on Jordan River Parkway, 1980 June 30 (Video 61)
  - KSL editorials, 1980 July-1980 August; DVD (Disc 13)
    - Another point of view (J. Francis Valerga), 1980 July 1 (Video 1)
    - Automobiles, gasoline, and mass transit, 1980 July 2 (Video 2)
    - Things are tough all over, 1980 July 3 (Video 3)
    - We need a sense of history, 1980 July 4 (Video 4)
    - Mideast oil and the USSR, 1980 July 5 (Video 5)
    - Television viewing and reading, 1980 July 6 (Video 6)
    - End the traffic light confusion, 1980 July 7 (Video 7)
    - The economy under attack, 1980 July 8 (Video 8)
    - Blackmail on the highways, 1980 July 9 (Video 9)
    - Windfall: profits or penalties, 1980 July 10 (Video 10)
    - A test for exclusionary rule, 1980 July 11 (Video 11)
    - Cholestrol or not cholestrol, 1980 July 12 (Video 12)
    - Go slow on year-round schools, 1980 July 13 (Video 13)
    - Realities of tax cutting, 1980 July 14 (Video 14)
    - Another point of view (Kent Harrison), 1980 July 15 (Video 15)
    - Are we frightened of our own freedom (moved to August 10 due to programming conflict), 1980 July 16 (Video 16)
    - Unions, power, and progress, 1980 July 17 (Video 17)
    - Energy Mobilization Board, 1980 July 18 (Video 18)
    - Today, the hot water; tomorrow..., 1980 July 19 (Video 19)
    - Planning for the eighties, 1980 July 20 (Video 20)
    - The fight against cancer, 1980 July 21 (Video 21)
    - Another point of view (Ken Olson), 1980 July 22 (Video 22)
    - Their thoughts are on the future, 1980 July 23 (Video 23)
    - The irony of history, 1980 July 24 (Video 24)
    - Common sense and the rules, 1980 July 25 (Video 25)
    - Creativity among consumers, 1980 July 26 (Video 26)
    - The impact of TV news, 1980 July 27 (Video 27)
    - The Ku Klux Klan in California, 1980 July 28 (Video 28)
    - Another point of view (Ken Olson), 1980 July 29 (Video 29)
    - Who pays for the jail?, 1980 July 30 (Video 30)
    - Natural gas from Alaska, 1980 July 31 (Video 31)
    - Idaho search threatens freedom, 1980 August 1 (Video 32)
    - Open invitation to crime, 1980 August 2 (Video 33)
    - There ought to be a law, 1980 August 3 (Video 34)
    - Recognizing tomorrow's leaders, 1980 August 4 (Video 35)
    - Fort Douglas: a question of value, 1980 August 5 (Video 36)
    - MX comes one step closer, 1980 August 6 (Video 37)
    - Reduce the greatest tax, 1980 August 7 (Video 38)
    - Suggestions for "future-gates", 1980 August 8 (Video 39)
    - You can't buck a friend, 1980 August 9 (Video 40)
    - Are we frightened of freedoms? (Rescheduled from 7/16), 1980 August 10 (Video 41)
    - Trucks on the highway, 1980 August 11 (Video 42)
    - Surprising facts about income tax, 1980 August 12 (Video 43)
    - Safety program for motorcycles (not recorded for archive), 1980 June 13 (Video 44)
    - Keeping social security secure, 1980 August 14 (Video 45)
    - Suggestions for Motor Vehicle Division, 1980 August 15 (Video 46)
    - Synthetic fuels and government money, 1980 August 16 (Video 47)
    - Congratulations on tax restraint, 1980 August 17 (Video 48)
    - Birthday for supermarkets, 1980 August 18 (Video 49)
    - To see that which has never been, 1980 August 19 (Video 50)
    - Another point of view (Ed Firmage), 1980 August 20 (Video 51)
    - Shakespeare and Cedar City, 1980 August 21 (Video 52)
    - The tragedy of child abuse, 1980 August 22 (Video 53)
    - The oil boom of the '80s, 1980 August 23 (Video 54)
    - The promise of the silicon chip, 1980 August 24 (Video 55)
    - More days on Joranelle, 1980 August 25 (Video 56)
    - Surprising record of postal service, 1980 August 26 (Video 57)
    - Reorganize Public Service Commission, 1980 August 27 (Video 58)
    - Encourage the study of foreign languages, 1980 August 28 (Video 59)
    - Expect another telephone rate increase, 1980 August 29 (Video 60)
    - What we think we know, 1980 August 30 (Video 61)
    - The high cost of welfare, 1980 August 31 (Video 62)
  - KSL editorials, 1980 September-1980 October; DVD (Disc 14)
    - Removing the obstacles of coal, 1980 September 1 (Video 1)
    - The struggle for a better life, 1980 September 2 (Video 2)
    - Sales tax and your pocketbook, 1980 September 3 (Video 3)
    - The benefits of genetic engineering, 1980 September 4 (Video 4)
    - Metered phone rates make sense, 1980 September 5 (Video 5)
    - Shade and the solar collector, 1980 September 6 (Video 6)
    - Reactions to sniper shootings, 1980 September 7 (Video 7)
    - Government power vs. private power, 1980 September 8 (Video 8)
    - Salt Lake artists want art space, 1980 September 9 (Video 9)
    - Approve voted leeway for Davis County, 1980 September 10 (Video 10)
    - Time to upgrade State Fairgrounds, 1980 September 11 (Video 11)
    - Welcome to Varujian Kojian, 1980 September 12 (Video 12)
    - Emphasize 'cure' over 'care', 1980 September 13 (Video 13)
    - Send your children to work, 1980 September 14 (Video 14)
    - Zoning and airport traffic, 1980 September 15 (Video 15)
    - Another point of view (Mike Shane), 1980 September 16 (Video 16)
    - Tax sale laws need revision, 1980 September 17 (Video 17)
    - Follow that bicycle, 1980 September 18 (Video 18)
    - The dilemma of federal funding, 1980 September 19 (Video 19)
    - When government goes berserk, 1980 September 20 (Video 20)
    - Are auto safety inspections worth it?, 1980 September 21 (Video 21)
    - The misuse of a mistaken "fact", 1980 September 22 (Video 22)
    - Another point of view (Jack Olson), 1980 September 23 (Video 23)
    - Revise the health care system, 1980 September 24 (Video 24)
    - Telephone companies in competitive struggle, 1980 September 25 (Video 25)
    - The United States and developing nations, 1980 September 26 (Video 26)
    - Delaney Law needs revision, 1980 September 27 (Video 27)
    - Time to call their bluff, 1980 September 28 (Video 28)
    - Danger signs for housing industry, 1980 September 29 (Video 29)
    - Another point of view (Heloyce Hamilton), 1980 September 30 (Video 30)
    - Another point of view (Bruce Thoren), 1980 October 1 (Video 31)
    - Washington speak with forked tongue, 1980 October 2 (Video 32)
    - Loan brokers must be licensed, 1980 October 3 (Video 33)
    - Musicians and their leaders, 1980 October 4 (Video 34)
    - Limits on lawmakers, 1980 October 5 (Video 35)
    - Tax law changes on Utah ballot, 1980 October 6 (Video 36)
    - Successes in the environment, 1980 October 7 (Video 37)
    - Meeting the school population challenge, 1980 October 8 (Video 38)
    - Putting productivity in perspective, 1980 October 9 (Video 39)
    - Increase vocational education efforts, 1980 October 10 (Video 40)
    - The threat of "little wars", 1980 October 11 (Video 41)
    - The growing shortage of workers, 1980 October 12 (Video 42)
    - Reject initiative proposal 'b', 1980 October 13 (Video 43)
    - Small cars and the speed limit, 1980 October 14 (Video 44)
    - Vote wisely on Board of Education, 1980 October 15 (Video 45)
    - Propositions on Utah Ballot, 1980 October 16 (Video 46)
    - Hunting season begins, 1980 October 17 (Video 47)
    - Our role in the Middle East, 1980 October 18 (Video 48)
    - Back to school basics, 1980 October 19 (Video 49)
    - False promise of sales tax removal, 1980 October 20 (Video 50)
    - Another point of view (Mike Shane), 1980 October 21 (Video 51)
    - Flaws in the tax limitation proposal, 1980 October 22 (Video 52)
    - Another viewpoint (Austin Belnap), 1980 October 23 (Video 53)
    - United Nations' anniversary, 1980 October 24 (Video 54)
    - Another point of view (Arlinda Parr), 1980 October 25 (Video 55)
    - Utah voters information pamphlet (not recorded for archive), 1980 October 26 (Video 56)
    - Another viewpoint (Paul Wharton), 1980 October 27 (Video 57)
    - Another viewpoint (Mike Shane)(not recorded for archive), 1980 October 28 (Video 58)
    - Another viewpoint (Blaine Zollinger)(not recorded for archive), 1980 October 29 (Video 59)
    - Another point of view (Paul Wharton)(not recorded for archive), 1980 October 30 (Video 60)
    - Another viewpoint (Frank Gunnell), 1980 October 31 (Video 61)
  - KSL editorials, 1980 November-1980 December; DVD (Disc 15)
    - Another point of view (Arlinda Parr), 1980 November 1 (Video 1)
    - Utah voter participation, 1980 November 2 (Video 2)
    - Government by the people, 1980 November 3 (Video 3)
    - Burning issues of election day, 1980 November 4 (Video 4)
    - Brazil moves on oil shale, 1980 November 5 (Video 5)
    - The tragedy of teenage suicide, 1980 November 6 (Video 6)
    - Change election practices, 1980 November 7 (Video 7)
    - The missing balanced budget, 1980 November 8 (Video 8)
    - The need for personal involvement, 1980 November 9 (Video 9)
    - The value of a great teacher, 1980 November 10 (Video 10)
    - The real victims of abscam, 1980 November 11 (Video 11)
    - Another point of view (Attorney General Robert Hansen), 1980 November 12 (Video 12)
    - Census of noncensus?, 1980 November 13 (Video 13)
    - At last, the voting machine, 1980 November 14 (Video 14)
    - Politics and the modern age, 1980 November 15 (Video 15)
    - Savings in state government, 1980 November 16 (Video 16)
    - The shameful voter turnout, 1980 November 17 (Video 17)
    - Limits on bureaucratic lawmaking, 1980 November 18 (Video 18)
    - Another point of view (Earl Vanfleet), 1980 November 19 (Video 19)
    - Monroe turns back to coal, 1980 November 20 (Video 20)
    - Utah's precarious financial position, 1980 November 21 (Video 21)
    - Alaskans battle the feds, 1980 November 22 (Video 22)
    - Utah Education Association Program, 1980 November 23 (Video 23)
    - Progress on scholar exchanges, 1980 November 24 (Video 24)
    - Statewide reappraisal program, 1980 November 25 (Video 25)
    - Our bountiful harvest, 1980 November 26 (Video 26)
    - Three thanksgivings, 1980 November 27 (Video 27)
    - Our first look at Saturn, 1980 November 28 (Video 28)
    - Cost benefits of safety (delayed to December 26 due to scheduling conflict) (not recorded for archive), 1980 November 29 (Video 29)
    - Good news about the economy, 1980 November 30 (Video 30)
    - The future of U.T.A., 1980 December 1 (Video 31)
    - Another point of view (Ben Ivey), 1980 December 2 (Video 32)
    - Political action committee 'hit list', 1980 December 3 (Video 33)
    - Another point of view (John Burton), 1980 December 4 (Video 34)
    - No restrictions on auto imports, 1980 December 5 (Video 35)
    - Utah needs new bankruptcy laws, 1980 December 6 (Video 36)
    - "The cost of good intentions", 1980 December 7 (Video 37)
    - UNESCO assails press freedom, 1980 December 8 (Video 38)
    - Raise pay for Utah judges, 1980 December 9 (Video 39)
    - Time to scrap the C.P.I., 1980 December 10 (Video 40)
    - Goals of bilingual education, 1980 December 11 (Video 41)
    - Revolution in Poland, 1980 December 12 (Video 42)
    - Progress on school problems, 1980 December 13 (Video 43)
    - A time for statesmanship, 1980 December 14 (Video 44)
    - Support emergency number 911, 1980 December 15 (Video 45)
    - Change voter registration rules, 1980 December 16 (Video 46)
    - Grandstanding on snow removal, 1980 December 17 (Video 47)
    - Salt Lake transportation studies, 1980 December 18 (Video 48)
    - Quarters for Christmas, 1980 December 19 (Video 49)
    - The 96th congress, 1980 December 20 (Video 50)
    - Teenage leaders offer promise, 1980 December 21 (Video 51)
    - The value of a fire code, 1980 December 22 (Video 52)
    - A.G. seeks to subvert legislature, 1980 December 23 (Video 53)
    - Christmas Eve, 1980 December 24 (Video 54)
    - Christmas Day, 1980 December 25 (Video 55)
    - Cost benefits of safety, 1980 December 26 (Video 56)
    - Plain english for I.R.S. (should be "will it reduce paperwork) (a different editorial was broadcast, but archivist recorded the wrong editorial), 1980 December 27 (Video 57)
    - Libel and public officials (actual broadcast: "disparity in air fares) (a different editorial was broadcast, but archivist recorded the wrong editorial), 1980 December 28 (Video 58)
    - Property tax equalization (actual broadcast: "another viewpoint - Senator Verl Asay") (a different editorial was broadcast, but archivist recorded the wrong editorial), 1980 December 29 (Video 59)
    - Another point of view (Charles Bollard, Disabled American Vets.) (actually broadcast: "another point of view - Mayor Paul Thompson) (a different editorial was broadcast, but archivist recorded the wrong editorial), 1980 December 30 (Video 60)
    - Value of anniversaries (actually broadcast: "New Year's Eve") (a different editorial was broadcast, but archivist recorded the wrong editorial), 1980 December 31 (Video 61)
  - KSL editorials, 1981 January-1981 February; DVD (Disc 16)
    - New Year's Day, 1981 January 1 (Video 1)
    - Why taxpayers are angry, 1981 January 2 (Video 2)
    - Libel and public officials (see Dec. 28, 1980) (editorial was broadcast as scheduled, but recorded on different date), 1981 January 3 (Video 3)
    - Plain english for the I.R.S. (see Dec. 27, 1980) (editorial was broadcast as scheduled, but recorded on different date), 1981 January 4 (Video 4)
    - Property tax equalization (see Dec. 29, 1980) (editorial was broadcast as scheduled, but recorded on different date), 1981 January 5 (Video 5)
    - Another viewpoint - Charles Bollard (see Dec. 30, 1980) (editorial was broadcast as scheduled, but recorded on different date), 1981 January 6 (Video 6)
    - The value of anniversaries (see Dec. 31, 1980) (editorial was broadcast as scheduled, but recorded on different date), 1981 January 7 (Video 7)
    - Another viewpoint - Gene Lambert, 1981 January 8 (Video 8)
    - Budget recommendations, 1981 January 9 (Video 9)
    - The storage of nuclear waste, 1981 January 10 (Video 10)
    - Problems for the legislature, 1981 January 11 (Video 11)
    - Shortcomings of the courts (not recoreded for archive), 1981 January 12 (Video 12)
    - Another viewpoint - Don Wilcox, letter carriers, 1981 January 13 (Video 13)
    - Don't change open meetings law, 1981 January 14 (Video 14)
    - Another viewpoint - Tony Brodman, 1981 January 15 (Video 15)
    - Congress has its own problems, 1981 January 16 (Video 16)
    - Another point of view - F.B.I., 1981 January 17 (Video 17)
    - Good news about education, 1981 January 18 (Video 18)
    - Misleading information about MX, 1981 January 19 (Video 19)
    - Lessons of inauguration day, 1981 January 20 (Video 20)
    - Regulators block court calendar, 1981 January 21 (Video 21)
    - What about social security? (Not recorded for archive), 1981 January 22 (Video 22)
    - Lessons from the power outage, 1981 January 23 (Video 23)
    - When it's right, it's wrong, 1981 January 24 (Video 24)
    - The end of the hostage ordeal, 1981 January 25 (Video 25)
    - Signal to the firefighters' union, 1981 January 26 (Video 26)
    - Another viewpoint - Sherm Ruesch, 1981 January 27 (Video 27)
    - On the subject of judicial pay (not recorded for archive), 1981 January 28 (Video 28)
    - The legislature and U.T.A., 1981 January 29 (Video 29)
    - Review senate bill 134, 1981 January 30 (Video 30)
    - Lessons from the Chrysler Affair, 1981 January 31 (Video 31)
    - February is Black History Month, 1981 February 1 (Video 32)
    - Cameras in the courtroom, 1981 February 2 (Video 33)
    - Don't condemn all Iranians, 1981 February 3 (Video 34)
    - Another viewpoint - Dr. Clark Puffer, UEA, 1981 February 4 (Video 35)
    - Legislature should revise taxes, 1981 February 5 (Video 36)
    - Protect higher education budget, 1981 February 6 (Video 37)
    - A Rembrandt it isn't, 1981 February 7 (Video 38)
    - English as a second language, 1981 February 8 (Video 39)
    - Primary Children's Medical Center, 1981 February 9 (Video 40)
    - Another viewpoint - Lt. Cal Cantonwine, firefighters union, 1981 February 10 (Video 41)
    - Chiefs of police protection bill, 1981 February 11 (Video 42)
    - Another viewpoint - Don Wilcox, retirement fund, 1981 February 12 (Video 43)
    - Learn to live with radar, 1981 February 13 (Video 44)
    - The eastern water shortage, 1981 February 14 (Video 45)
    - End reign of terror, 1981 February 15 (Video 46)
    - Preserve public education, 1981 February 16 (Video 47)
    - Time for more SALT negotiations, 1981 February 17 (Video 48)
    - Another viewpoint - Senator Verl Asay, judicial pay, 1981 February 18 (Video 49)
    - Maintain kindergarten program, 1981 February 19 (Video 50)
    - Bills to ignore, 1981 February 20 (Video 51)
    - Cub scouts deliver the mail, 1981 February 21 (Video 52)
    - International terrorism, 1981 February 22 (Video 53)
    - Formalize State Department of Health, 1981 February 23 (Video 54)
    - Help for the handicapped, 1981 February 24 (Video 55)
    - Here comes Susan B. again, 1981 February 25 (Video 56)
    - Table senate bill 134, 1981 February 26 (Video 57)
    - Time for a severance tax, 1981 February 27 (Video 58)
    - MX clears more hurdles, 1981 February 28 (Video 59)
  - KSL editorials, 1981 March-1981 April; DVD (Disc 17)
    - Another viewpoint - Robert Wright, 1981 March 1 (Video 1)
    - Dangers in utility regulation, 1981 March 2 (Video 2)
    - Another viewpoint - Ivan Heslop, bank vice president, 1981 March 3 (Video 3)
    - Travel to the Soviet Union, 1981 March 4 (Video 4)
    - Another viewpoint - Earl Jeppson, american party, 1981 March 5 (Video 5)
    - Increase the gasoline tax, 1981 March 6 (Video 6)
    - Keep sales tax distribution, 1981 March 7 (Video 7)
    - Few dollars, many projects, 1981 March 8 (Video 8)
    - Another viewpoint - Sen. K. Swan, 1981 March 9 (Video 9)
    - Another viewpoint - Lee McDonald, 1981 March 10 (Video 10)
    - Another viewpoint - Mayor Paul Thompson, 1981 March 11 (Video 11)
    - Limit legislative bills, 1981 March 12 (Video 12)
    - Military personnel needs critical, 1981 March 13 (Video 13)
    - Citizens share the blame, 1981 March 14 (Video 14)
    - Supply side economics, 1981 March 15 (Video 15)
    - Freedom of information day, 1981 March 16 (Video 16)
    - The behavior of school teachers, 1981 March 17 (Video 17)
    - Another viewpoint - Ed Firmage, MX missile opposition, 1981 March 18 (Video 18)
    - Turmoil in El Salvador, 1981 March 19 (Video 19)
    - Farm week in Utah, 1981 March 20 (Video 20)
    - Time for a tax cut (not recorded for archive), 1981 March 21 (Video 21)
    - Whatever it takes for Atlanta (not recorded for archive), 1981 March 22 (Video 22)
    - Utah's Repertory Dance Theatre (not recorded for archive), 1981 March 23 (Video 23)
    - Another viewpoint - Joseph Stumph, Jr. (not recorded for archive), 1981 March 24 (Video 24)
    - Danger in the middle east (not recorded for archive), 1981 March 25 (Video 25)
    - Capitalism in the Soviet Union (not recorded for archive), 1981 March 26 (Video 26)
    - Time for a summit meeting, 1981 March 27 (Video 27)
    - Nuclear energy passed a test, 1981 March 28 (Video 28)
    - We must not adapt to crime, 1981 March 29 (Video 29)
    - Support for the arts, 1981 March 30 (Video 30)
    - Another viewpoint - Donna Peterson, 1981 March 31 (Video 31)
    - No change on C.U.P., 1981 April 1 (Video 32)
    - Alternatives to nursing homes, 1981 April 2 (Video 33)
    - Support for the arts (not recorded for archive), 1981 April 3 (Video 34)
    - Knowledge of the constitution (not recorded for archive), 1981 April 4 (Video 35)
    - Citizens and government waste (not recorded for archive), 1981 April 5 (Video 36)
    - The attack on the president (not recorded for archive), 1981 April 6 (Video 37)
    - The trend towards elitism (not recorded for archive), 1981 April 7 (Video 38)
    - Carol Burnett and the Enquirer, 1981 April 8 (Video 39)
    - Legislative action shortsighted, 1981 April 9 (Video 40)
    - Plans for county jail, 1981 April 10 (Video 41)
    - Your share of the tax burden, 1981 April 11 (Video 42)
    - N.A.B. Distinguished Service Award (to Arch Madsen), 1981 April 12 (Video 43)
    - Sunday bus service, 1981 April 13 (Video 44)
    - Pressure for gun control, 1981 April 14 (Video 45)
    - Commendation for S.L. police, 1981 April 15 (Video 46)
    - Study plan for the legislature, 1981 April 16 (Video 47)
    - The space shuttle is a beginning, 1981 April 17 (Video 48)
    - The legislature and education, 1981 April 18 (Video 49)
    - Is the zoo doomed?, 1981 April 19 (Video 50)
    - Voluntary vehicle inspection program, 1981 April 20 (Video 51)
    - Another viewpoint - Kenneth Olsen, MX proponent, 1981 April 21 (Video 52)
    - Spring: a time when..., 1981 April 22 (Video 53)
    - Demands on the justice system, 1981 April 23 (Video 54)
    - Irresponsible pet owners, 1981 April 24 (Video 55)
    - Victims of the grain embargo, 1981 April 25 (Video 56)
    - If you love your child, 1981 April 26 (Video 57)
    - Why teachers become discouraged, 1981 April 27 (Video 58)
    - Salt Palace expansion needed, 1981 April 28 (Video 59)
    - When justice is frustrated, 1981 April 29 (Video 60)
    - Clean Air Day in Utah, 1981 April 30 (Video 61)
  - KSL editorials, 1981 May-1981 June; DVD (Disc 18)
    - The FAA sets a bad exmaple (not recorded for archive), 1981 May 1 (Video 1)
    - Benefits for one in three, 1981 May 2 (Video 2)
    - Oppose tuition tax credits, 1981 May 3 (Video 3)
    - Incentives for better teaching, 1981 May 4 (Video 4)
    - American 'hostages' in Vietnam, 1981 May 5 (Video 5)
    - Effects of the sagebrush revolution, 1981 May 6 (Video 6)
    - High school career days, 1981 May 7 (Video 7)
    - Salt Lake City budget, 1981 May 8 (Video 8)
    - Skagway and EPA nonsense, 1981 May 9 (Video 9)
    - Good judgment on fund drives, 1981 May 10 (Video 10)
    - Hold fast to ABM treaty, 1981 May 11 (Video 11)
    - Another point of view - Dale Mooso, 1981 May 12 (Video 12)
    - "What you see is...", 1981 May 13 (Video 13)
    - The high cost of justice, 1981 May 14 (Video 14)
    - Public opninion about schools, 1981 May 15 (Video 15)
    - Armed forces day, 1981 May 16 (Video 16)
    - Time for child-proof neighborhoods, 1981 May 17 (Video 17)
    - Cable television and "decency", 1981 May 18 (Video 18)
    - Courtesy in the sports, 1981 May 19 (Video 19)
    - Make punishment fit the crime, 1981 May 20 (Video 20)
    - The American red cross, 1981 May 21 (Video 21)
    - Our commitment to education, 1981 May 22 (Video 22)
    - Driving safety and alcohol (not recorded for archive), 1981 May 23 (Video 23)
    - Social security changes needed (not recorded for archive), 1981 May 24 (Video 24)
    - How to beat the lights (not recorded for archive), 1981 May 25 (Video 25)
    - Mayor's tax study plan (not recorded for archive), 1981 May 26 (Video 26)